<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>untu</title>
    <link>http://untu.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on untu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 17:29:03 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://untu.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Macbook Windows</title>
      <link>http://untu.org/posts/macbook-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 17:29:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://untu.org/posts/macbook-windows/</guid>
      <description>Due to a factory recall of sorts, Apple replaced my motherboard in my 2011 MacBook Pro. After already purchasing a newer one when it originally failed, I needed to decide what to do with my newly refurbished laptop. Having already upgraded it to 16gb of RAM years ago, it was far too capable to just forget about it. While I prefer MacOS for almost everything, there is some software development (aka coding or programming) that is best done on Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Outward Appearance</title>
      <link>http://untu.org/posts/outward-appearance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 00:29:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://untu.org/posts/outward-appearance/</guid>
      <description>The bible says, “Oh man, who art thou that replies against God? Shall the thing formed say to him that formed it, Why has thou made me thus? Has not the potter power over the clay, of the same lump to make one vessel unto honor, and another unto dishonor?” &amp;ndash; Romans Chapter 9
Yet, in spite of the clear warning that mankind lacks accurate spiritual vision, we still judge situations, even though only God Himself has true clarity of vision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monsters are Real</title>
      <link>http://untu.org/posts/monsters-are-real/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2013 23:03:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://untu.org/posts/monsters-are-real/</guid>
      <description>My favorite TV show these days is the BBC series: Doctor Who. The show is British Science Fiction/Comedy. It’s done in a way that only the Brits can pull off. Anyway, there was an episode last season called “Night Terrors”. In the first part of the episode, The Doctor exclaims, “Monsters are Real!”. While that was not the best episode of the season, it is one of the most memorable lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Year 13</title>
      <link>http://untu.org/posts/the-year-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 21:46:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://untu.org/posts/the-year-13/</guid>
      <description>So here we are in 2013, now thirteen years after many Christians had anticipated the Lord’s return. Yet, here we are. The year &amp;ldquo;13&amp;rdquo;, so far, is a bad one: The Supreme Court is actually considering if gay marriage should be a constitutionally protected right; Similarly, with the ObamaCare tax, all Americans are mandated to fund abortions. In year 13, it’s more difficult for a 13-year-old girl to buy a pack of cigarettes than to get an abortion (and most Americans seem to believe that cigarettes are worse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charity Sings</title>
      <link>http://untu.org/posts/charity-sings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2013 00:53:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://untu.org/posts/charity-sings/</guid>
      <description>A man that has friends must show himself friendly &amp;ndash; Proverbs 18:24a
Conservative Christians have been known to ridicule some of their more liberal counterparts by suggesting that they place too much emphasis on “Love”. However, I suggest that such ridicule is unwarranted. The KJV word for “Love” is “Charity”. Charity is a sacrificial love which is why the modern-day meaning of “charity” is equated with “giving”. Accordingly, when you see “charity” in the passage below, it should be understood to mean “sacrificial love”:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
